waytoindia.com 2015-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Waytoindia

Welcome to the Comfort Connections Group websites(i.e waytoindia.com, waytopunjab.com, waytogoa.com, waytorajasthan.com, waytotaj.com, triptochardham.com, bestkeralatrip.com, luxurycabsindia.com, comfortconnections.net) (hereinafter referred to as the "Websites"). These Websites are an internet property of Comfort Connections Pvt Ltd. ("Comfort Connections", "we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Website. Please read this notice carefully. ...

###  I. PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you visit our Websites and you provide us with your personal information such as email address, your name, zip code and telephone number, we will not disclose that personal information to any third party without your consent, except to a third party as required, that might assist us to help us distribute correspondence from us to you. However, in order to cooperate with legitimate governmental requests, subpoenas, or court orders, to protect Comfort Connections and/or Comfort Connections’s customers and/or promoters,employees, or to ensure the integrity and operation of Comfort Connections and/or Comfort Connections’s business and systems, we may access and disclose any information we consider necessary or appropriate under the circumstances.By opting to our email database you expressly give your consent to receiving our newsletters and promotional mails.

Please note that we do not consider aggregated information, from which personally identifiable information has been removed, to be personal information. We may share the aggregated information about our users for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

In addition, when you visit our Website, our web server may automatically recognize your domain name. We collect the domain name and monitor general site use and traffic patterns to improve our Website and the products and services we offer. We also may use web server logs to collect data for metric purposes. Examples of the types of data collected on the logs are IP addresses, referral pages, date and time of Site access, and Site visited. We may use collected data to customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor.

###  II. CHOICE/OPT-OUT

If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices.

###  III. COOKIES AND/OR TRACERS

Cookies are small data files placed on your hard drive by a website server when you visit. We may use cookies for tracking purposes or to make our Website easier to use. Cookies are currently the only way to effectively identify a unique anonymous visitor and understand how they navigate our web site. An anonymous visitor to our site remains anonymous in all cases. We do not attempt to identify visitors if they do not voluntarily submit personal information to us. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Cookies offer enhanced functionality to the user, but whether you allow a cookie to be placed on your computer is up to you!

In some instances, we may use tracking scripts or "tracers" that recognize a unique identifier from a cookie placed on your hard drive by another website. These are used by us solely to gauge the success of our own advertising. For instance, we may use a tracer to determine whether you visit our employment pages after visiting a resume or career site where we placed a banner ad. We do not use tracers to gather information on your use of the internet unrelated to us. We may also use your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, such as your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university, to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, serve you more relevant offers and administer our Website. Please note that we do not use tracers to identify your personal information, and you remain anonymous unless and until you choose to identify yourself.

###  IV. SECURITY

We do not treat your general interaction with Comfort Connections (e.g., submission of suggestions) as confidential. Any information you submit will be treated as non- confidential. Note that most internet browsers also offer security alerts that permit you to determine whether your transmissions are protected.

###  V. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

Some of the ads appearing on this Website are delivered to you by our web advertising partners. Information about your visit to their site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you.

###  VI. CHILDREN

Comfort Connections is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the Website, provide any personal information or receive our email distributions. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the Website or receiving emails.

###  VII. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

As part of the service, Comfort Connections may create links allowing you to access third party sites. Comfort Connections is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

###  VIII. MODIFICATION TO THIS POLICY

We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time; however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page so please check back. If you continue to access this Website that will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

Thank you for taking the time and interest to review our policies at Comfort Connections. If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of this Privacy Policy, please email us at info [at] waytoindia [dot] com. We welcome your questions and feedback.
